David Vasko

Phone: (858) 610-0566 Email: vasko6d@gmail.com Website: david.vaskos.com

Overview

Avid rock climber with a passion for programming in Machine Learning applications: Image Recognition, NLU, Computer Vision, Autonomous Navigation Systems and other Deep Learning topics. Coming from 2 years of industry experience with practical application of Facial Recognition in EMPI Matching Algorithms I want to continue pursuing similar challenges.

Education

Masters of Science: UCLA Graduated June 2015

Major: Aerospace Engineering (3.68 GPA)

Focus: Systems and Control

Bachelors of Science: UCLA Graduated June 2014

Major: Mechanical Engineering (3.89 GPA, Summa Cum Laude)

Technical Breadth: Computer Science

Work Experience

Solutions Architect: NextGate Solutions

March 2016 - March 2018

Worked with Java, Java EE, and internet technologies (AngularJS) to create and maintain Java and Web applications for customers and for NextGate. Notable projects include: EMPI Implementation and Integration for Ascension Health, EMPI Implementation and Data Integration for Northern Territories Australia; and Facial Recognition for identification and patient matching.

SolidWorks 2014 Beta Support: Dassault Systemès

Summer 2013

Direct line of support with customers for the SolidWorks 2014 Beta at the Woodland Hills office in Los Angeles.

Teaching Assistant: UCLA

Fall 2014 - Winter 2016

Administrated labs and discussions for both the Mechanical Engineering and Life Science departments. Awarded "Certificate of Distinction in Teaching" by the UCLA Life Sciences Division.

Rockwall Supervisor: UCLA Recreation

Spring 2013 – Spring 2014

Notable Projects

- Facial Recognition for EMPI Matching Algorithms Python, Docker, Java, ZeroMQ, OpenFace, Torch and Lua
- Autonomous collection and deployment robot LabView, SolidWorks
- 3D sandbox game JavaScript and webGL
- Finite element solver for membranes under plane stress condition MATLAB
- Finite volume solver for 2D flow MATLAB

Programming Languages and Technologies

- Python, Java, C++, MATLAB, R, JavaScript, LabView, Lisp, SQL, Ruby, bash, sed
- Docker, WebGL, AngularJS, ReactJS, Node, OSGi, Ruby on Rails, Apache Camel, Apache Karaf

References

- Gevik Nalbandian, VP of Software Engineering at NextGate zgev@yahoo.com
- Dan Cidon, CTO at NextGate dan.cidon@nextgate.com
- Tony Tsao, Senior Manager at Dassault Systèmes Solidworks tonytsao@gmail.com
- Will Conley, Math Professor at UCLA wconley@ucla.edu